question_data = [
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Typewriter; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Coca-Cola;s original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The word news; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
